http://www.wimort.com/privacy-policy

Youtube
262.786.5250Contact UsLog In
Mortgage BasicsWhat is a Pre-ApprovalChoose the Right MortgageTips to Easy QualificationClean Up Those Credit IssuesLoan Process OverviewWhat to GatherResourcesFirst Time HomebuyerRefinance InformationSecure Document UploadRates and CostsGlossaryFind a Loan OfficerAboutCalculatorsApply Now
Home›Privacy Policy
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal information. Please read this note carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: 
Social Security number and names
Addresses and Subject property contract information
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their every day business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Wisconsin Mortgage Corporation chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus.
Can Wisconsin Mortgage Corporation share? Yes
Can you limit this sharing? No
For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you.
Can Wisconsin Mortgage Corporation share? Yes
Can you limit this sharing? No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Can Wisconsin Mortgage Corporation share? No
Can you limit this sharing? No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – Information
about your transactions and experiences.
Can Wisconsin Mortgage Corporation share? Yes
Can you limit this sharing? No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – Information
about your creditworthiness.
Can Wisconsin Mortgage Corporation share? No
Can you limit this sharing? No
For non-affiliates to market to you
Can Wisconsin Mortgage Corporation share? No
Can you limit this sharing? No
Questions?
Call 262.786.5250
Who We Are
Who is providing this notice?
Wisconsin Mortgage Corporation
What We Do
How does Wisconsin Mortgage Corporation protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does Wisconsin Mortgage Corporation collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you inquire about a mortgage or apply for a mortgage.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes-information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you

sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Non-Affiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Loan agent is set:
Clicking "Find a Loan Officer" in the main nav will take you directly to their "secret" page.
Clear this cookie to test another agent
